kusports.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy | KUsports.com

### Privacy and Use of Your Information

Any communication or material you transmit to the Website by electronic mail or otherwise, including any User Generated Content, is and will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. Anything you transmit or post on the Website may be used by KUSports.com or its affiliates for any purpose, including but not limited to reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication and posting. Furthermore, KUSports.com is free to use any ideas, concepts or techniques contained in any communication you send to the Website for any purpose whatsoever.

KUSports.com makes commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard individual Website users’ personal information. Nevertheless, KUSports.com cannot ensure that these measures will provide perfect security. KUSports.com will not be responsible or liable for damage, pecuniary or otherwise, caused by a third party’s unauthorized access to or use of your information.

You will not use the Website in any manner, or in connection with any User Generated Content provided by or on behalf of you or any person accessing a Website under your authority, that (1) infringes or violates any patent, copyright, trade secret, trademark, or other intellectual property right of any third party, or (2) violates any applicable international, federal, state or local law, rule, legislation, regulation of ordinance, including, without limitation, the Communications Decency Act of 1996, as amended.

Your use of the Website constitutes your agreement to respect other users’ privacy. You may not, under any circumstances, release personal information of others to third parties, including to your employees, without the written consent of both KUSports.com and the person or persons whose personal information you intend to share. You may not, under any circumstances, use personal information obtained from the Website to send unsolicited email, facsimile transmissions, chain letters, spam or any other communication or messages, even if the recipient has communicated with you in the past. You agree to immediately notify KUSports.com of any release or breach of any third party’s personal information (including name, address, phone numbers, email addresses, account numbers or social security number) that occurs as a result of use of a Website under your Account.

You may not do anything to interfere or attempt to interfere with any function of the Website. You may not take any action that overloads, places an unreasonable burden on or otherwise diminishes the functionality or responsiveness of the Website, which KUSports.com shall solely determine. Any attempt to alter information posted on a Website or to interfere with the Website will result in immediate termination of your right to access the Website and may also render you liable for civil and/or criminal penalties. 

### Information Gathered

KUSports.com gathers identifying information about Website users (“Information”) only when a user provides that information on a voluntary basis such as by registering for or using an Account, Alerts, RSS feeds, by posting User Generated Content, by using social networking tools and the like. KUSports.com does not sell, rent or lease user information to third parties. KUSports.com occasionally may share Information with its affiliates and related companies. If you choose to use social networking tools available on the Website, your favorites or other profile information may be shared with other Website users who also use those social networking tools.

KUSports.com periodically collects and analyzes log files, including IP addresses, from its servers. These files give a general picture of who is visiting the Website and which pages are being viewed most often. This information is collected to assist KUSports.com in the maintenance and administration of the Website. KUSports.com may share log file information with advertisers, but will refer only to general, aggregate usage data, not user specific identifying information.

The Website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on KUSports.com or the Website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of KUSports.com; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Website, or the public. Except as noted above, KUSports.com does not share any of the personal information you provide to us with any third party other than our service providers who assist us in providing information and/or services to you. 

KUSports.com also uses “cookie” technology that allows its servers to deposit codes on a user’s computer. This information helps determine the number of visitors to the Website on an ongoing basis and the types of Internet browsers and operating systems used by the Website’s users. This information is used to enhance your Website experience. 

### Third Parties 

KUSports.com offers to Website users social networking tools that may include “befriending” other users, updating Profile information, posting comments on other users' Profiles and identifying Website content or User Generated Content as something of interest to a particular user. When a user takes advantage of the social networking tools, the user agrees to share personal information with other users. KUSports.com provides privacy tools within its social networking framework to enable users to control the types of this personal information that is shared with other users. If you post User Generated Content to the Website that includes your User Name, email address or any other personally identifying information, you understand that that information can be read by any third party and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties.

### Process to Remove Your Personal Information

Most of KUSports.com’s services include information on how to remove your information, and/or and cancel a particular KUSports.com service. We do not generall delete or remove accounts. Alternatively, you may send an email to webmaster@KUSports.com to request the services and information you would like removed. Your request should include the specific reasons why KUSports.com should remove identified content. KUSports.com reserves the right to decline requests for removal of information based on maintaining the historical and archival nature of the Website.

_Updated April 2010_
